LUIS CABALLERO

Front-End Developer

CONTACT

Berlin Schöneberg Email hallo.luiscaballero@gmail.com Phone +49 176 8408 5303

luiscaballero84.github.io

ABOUT

Recent coding bootcamp graduate at Le Wagon Berlin with a background in brand design. Over 5 years of experience working as a graphic designer and 2 years as a freelance illustrator.

I am a very curious person, hardworking and always eager to learn, seeking for my first job opportunity a as front-end developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

March 2018 - Jan. 2020	Freelance graphic designer & illustrator in Berlin

www.madebyhorses.com

July 2015 - Oct. 2017 Graphic designer at The Marmalade, Hamburg

www.themarmalade.com

Responsible of the corporate design implementation within the company in all media, including the website (through a CMS and giving feedback to

developers).

Dec. 2013 – Jan. 2015 Graphic designer at Factor Design, Hamburg

www.factor.partners

Part of the branding development team with projects for clients such as

Gardena, Re/max, COR and Brot für die Welt.

Aug. 2011 - Oct. 2012 Brand Guardian Trainee at Siemens Healthcare, Brand Management

& Corporate Design, Erlangen

Controlling and proper implementation of the Siemens Corporate Design

Styleguides in all kind of physical media.

Nov. 2006 - Jan. 2010 Online Marketing Consultant at GoViral, Copenhagen

Responsible of the spanish market for the digital media implementation and

activation of brands like Nissan, Pepsi or 7Up.

PROJECTS

PlanYourNight. A mobile app for planning your best night outs

www.planyournight.xyz

PlanYourNight was my final project at Le Wagon. My main task in this team project was design and implement a nice and useful UX/UI experience for the end user.

EDUCATION

Jan. 2020 - March 2020	Full Stack Developer Bootcamp Le Wagon, Berlin
March 2011 - July 2011	DSH (Deutsche Sprachprüfung für den Hochschulzugang) Test Preparation Course Georg-Simon-Ohm-Hochschule, Nuremberg
May 2009 - Dec. 2009	Adobe Desktop Publishing Software Course CICE School, Madrid
Sept. 2002 – June 2008	Bachelor of Arts in Audiovisual Communication University of Sevilla
Sept. 2006 – June 2007	Completion of two semesters abroad through the ERASMUS Programm University of Copenhagen

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- > HTML & CSS
- > JavaScript
- > Bootstrap & SASS
- > Git
- > Figma
- > Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign
- > Glyphs

LANGUAGES

- > English Proficient/ Fluent
- > German Proficient/ Fluent
- > Spanish Native